http://www.niagaranationalcorp.com/index.php/legal_notice

Access and Use of Information
All access to and use of this website (the "Site") is governed by the terms and conditions provided below. Entering into this website indicates that you have reviewed and have agreed to be bound by these terms. Zep Inc. ("Zep") may make future changes or modifications to these terms and conditions at any time without notice and your subsequent viewing or use of the Site will constitute your agreement to the changes and modifications. There may be additional terms and conditions provided governing your use of particular functions, features, information and applications available through the Site.
All copyrights in the materials on this Site are owned by Zep. “Zep” and its other brand names, and its logos are trademarks of Zep, whether registered or not. All rights not expressly granted in these terms are reserved. This Site is provided for informational purposes only for Zep's customers, investors, vendors, employees and other constituencies and may not be used by any other person or entity, or for any other purpose. Any access or attempt to access other areas of the Zep computer system or other information contained on the system for any purposes is strictly prohibited. You may not use the Site in any manner whatsoever that could lead to a violation of any federal, state or local laws, rules or regulations. You may view, display, or print in hard copy form, a single copy of any of the content of this Site subject to the following conditions:
The materials may be used for personal and non-commercial use only in connection with a legitimate personal or business purpose.
Any copy of these materials or any portion thereof must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices.
Zep may revoke or modify any of the foregoing rights at any time.
Any further copying, downloading, publication or distribution of any part of this Site is prohibited. Please note that any product, process or technology described in these materials may be the subject of other intellectual property rights reserved by Zep and are not licensed hereunder. Zep does not convey to anyone, through allowing access to the Site, any ownership rights in the Site or in any content appearing on or made available through the Site. This Site contains many Zep and third party trademarks and service marks. All marks are property of their respective companies. No license to use or reproduce any of these trademarks is given or implied. These trademarks may not be copied, downloaded, reproduced, used, modified, or distributed in any way (except as an integral part of an authorized copy of material appearing in these web pages, as provided above) without prior written permission.
No Warranty
All information provided on this Site may be changed, updated or deleted without notice. While efforts have been made to make this Site helpful and accurate, it could contain technical inaccuracies or other errors, or be outdated and Zep does not warrant the accuracy, completeness or timeliness of information obtained from this Site.
THE SITE AND ITS CONTENT ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" FOR YOUR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. ZEP DOES NOT WARRANT THAT FUNCTIONS CONTAINED ON THIS SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU BUT IS INTENDED TO APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWABLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. USE OF THE SITE AND ITS CONTENT IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.
Limitation of Damages
ZEP WILL IN NO EVENT BE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR OTHER DAMAGES UNDER ANY THEORY OF LAW FOR ANY ERRORS IN OR THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE AND ITS CONTENT (OR ANY HYPERLINKED WEB SITE) INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS, DATA, OR DAMAGE TO ANY COMPUTER SYSTEMS, EVEN IF YOU HAVE ADVISED ZEP OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU BUT IS INTENDED TO APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWABLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
Location
Zep controls and manages this website from its facilities in the State of Georgia in the United States of America. Unless otherwise stated, materials and content on this website are presented solely for promoting products and services in the United States. Information published on this website may contain references to products, programs and services that are not announced or available in your country or region. We make no representation that such information, products, programs or services referenced on this website are legal, available or appropriate in your country or region.
Links to and/or From the Site
From time to time, the Site may contain links to third party websites not controlled by Zep. Zep provides such links as a convenience to you, and in no way endorses such third party sites. Zep is not responsible for any aspect of the information or content contained on any third party sites accessible or linked to the Site. You may not “frame” or “mirror” any content or information contained on or accessible from the Site without the prior written approval of Acuity or its licensors, as may be appropriate.
Submitting information to Zep
Please see our Privacy Policy for general information. Zep does not accept ideas, concepts, or techniques for new services or products through the Site. Zep DOES NOT want to receive confidential or proprietary information from you through this Site. Any information that Zep receives through this Site, other than your personally identifiable information, as explained in Zep’s Privacy Policy, will be deemed to be NON-CONFIDENTIAL. By transmitting to Zep information via this Site or otherwise through electronic means, you grant to Zep an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, communicate, exploit, display, modify, perform and distribute such information, and Zep is free to use the information, including any ideas, know-how or techniques contained therein free of charge for any purpose whatsoever.
Securities and Investment
Neither this website nor the information contained or referred to herein constitutes an offer or a solicitation of an offer for the purchase or sale of any securities. This website may contain information and press releases about and by Zep that may include forward-looking statements, within the meaning of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Statements that may be considered forward-looking include statements incorporating terms such as “will”, “expects,” “believes”,” intends”, “anticipates” and similar terms that relate to future events, performance, or results of the company. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of the date they are made. Zep undertakes no obligation to update or revise any forward-looking statements. Forward-looking statements are subject to certain risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results, expectations or outcomes to differ materially from the historical experience of Zep and management’s present expectations.
Privacy Policy
The manner in which we collect and disseminate information is set forth in our Privacy Policy as updated from time to time and posted on this Site. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites, including without limitation, other websites owned by Zep, and we can take no responsibility for the information, collection or dissemination policies of third party. Your use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. You should not access the site if you do not agree with the terms of our Privacy Policy.
Legal Notice | Priviacy Policy
Copyright 2020 Zep Inc.
